<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2024-01-02T00:36:39-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Zeyu Yun</title><entry><title type="html">Note 004 Set/Function (20 mins read)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/cs70/2020/06/13/note005.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Note 004 Set/Function (20 mins read)" /><published>2020-06-13T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2020-06-13T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/cs70/2020/06/13/note005</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/cs70/2020/06/13/note005.html">&lt;h3 id=&quot;induction-does-not-always-work&quot;&gt;Induction does not always work!&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am going to prove a false Theorem, see if you can notice where the proves went wrong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Theorem&lt;/strong&gt;  The power set of \(\mathbb{N}\) is countable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Proof”&lt;/em&gt;  We proceed the induction on \(\mathbb{N}\)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Base case: k=0, \(\mathcal{P} (0) =  \emptyset\), which is indeed countable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Induction step: Assume that \(\mathcal{P}(n)\) is countable. We call it \(n+1th\) element as \(s_{n+1}\), then \(\mathcal{P}(n+1)\) can be broken down to a collection of sets that do not contain \(s_{n+1}\), and a collection of sets that contains \(s_{n+1}\) element. Clearly, the first collection is exactly \(\mathcal{P}(n)\), the second collection is every set in \(\mathcal{P}(n)\) with the addition of \(s_{n+1}\). Formally, \(\{ S \cup s_{n+1}  \mid S \in  \mathcal{P}(n) \}\) Since you learnt in the lecture that union of two countable set is countable. We proved that \(\mathcal{P}(n+1)\) is countable. So \(\mathcal{P}(\mathbb{N})\) is countable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Where’s wrong?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, first of all, which part of the proof did we do right?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Actually only the very last part is wrong! Did you get it? We proved that \(\forall n \in \mathbb{N} \mathcal{P}(n)\) is countable. More then that, it’s finite. If I give you any number, you can list out the powerset (using bit string). But that doesn’t mean \(\mathcal{P}(\mathbb{N})\) because \(\mathcal{P}(\mathbb{N})\) is infinite.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;axiom-of-choice&quot;&gt;Axiom of Choice&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(Try to read this part, if you don’t understand it, it’s fine because it’s outside the scope, but if you do understand it then you can assure that you will be doing really well in the class)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The idea of Axiom of choice is simple. It states that if you have a collection of sets, you can always select one element from each set. If you have finite amounts of those sets, even thought you can’t physically pick an element, you can still argue you can pick an element from each set one if it’s not empty until you did it to all sets. But what if we have infinite many of those sets? Can you pick an element from each set if there are infinite amount of sets?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The answer is unknown. At least you can’t prove it in mathematic without assuming stronger condition. Thus, it can be considered as an Axiom. You can whether accept it or not accept it. Mathematic are built upon Axioms. Just like “1+1 =2”, if you accept “1+1 =2” as an Axiom, you can prove a lot of nice things from it. If you don’t, then the mathematic world will be much more restricted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Formally,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Axiom of Choice&lt;/strong&gt;  Let \(\mathcal{C}\) be any collection of nonempty sets. Then there is a function \(F\) defined on \(\mathcal{C}\) which assigns to each set \(A \in \mathcal{C}\) an element \(F(A)\) in \(A\)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First daily excercise: Write out Axiom of Choice using proper propositional logic like you learnt in class.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Second daily excercise: Let \(f: X \to Y\) be a mapping onto Y. Show that the right inverse of f exist. In other word, show that you can find a function \(f^{-1}: Y \to X\) such that \(f (f^{-1}(a)) = a\) for all \(a \in A\)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This question looks intimidating but it’s not hard at all. Try to draw a picture of a onto function yourself. Here’s what I have:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/cs70_math/on_2.png&quot; alt=&quot;image info&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All we need to do is to find a one-to-one function that maps from the right to the left. (Why?) For this picture, it’s easy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/cs70_math/on.png&quot; alt=&quot;image info&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What about the general case?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hint 1: Try to break down the domain, X, into “A collection of sets”. What’s a natural break down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hint 2: Break down the the domain according to the image of each element in the domain, if to elements are mapped to the same thing, they should be in the same set.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hint 3: Consider the collection \(\{ A : (\exists y \in Y), A = f^{-1} [ \{ y \} ] \}\)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/cs70/w6.gif&quot; alt=&quot;image info&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s a daily dose of kirara.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Induction does not always work!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Note 003 Induction (5 mins read)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/cs70/2020/06/13/note003.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Note 003 Induction (5 mins read)" /><published>2020-06-13T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2020-06-13T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/cs70/2020/06/13/note003</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/cs70/2020/06/13/note003.html">&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-truth-behind-induction-hypothesis&quot;&gt;The Truth Behind Induction Hypothesis:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This will be in the lecture, in the note, everywhwere. But make sure you can write induction principle on your own and understand how this transforms into “proof by induction”:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Formal definition:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Induction Principle: \(P(1) \wedge (P(n) \implies P(n+1)) \implies \forall n \in \mathbb{N} P(n)\)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Essentially, we can expand “\(P(n) \implies P(n+1)\)”, as the following chain of implication is true:&lt;/p&gt;

\[P(1) \implies P(2) \implies P(3) \implies P(4) ...\]

&lt;p&gt;Since this chain of implication is true, if we know P(1) is True as well, then P(2) is True. Since P(2) True, then P(3) is True…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is just like a sequence of domino tiles, we now know every P(n) is true!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is formally why induction is true!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In fact, Induction Principle directly comes from “Well Ordering Principle” of integers, which is very nonempty subset of integers has a smallest or least element. In fact, you can prove “Well Ordering Principle” implies “Induction Principle”.Hint:[Use proof by contradiction and consider the set \(n \in \mathbb{N} P(n)\) is False]. I will leave this as a daily excercise to you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;induction-not-only-on-natural-number&quot;&gt;Induction not only on Natural number:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Can you do induction some set other than natural number? Absolutely, for example, consider the set \(3\mathbb{Z}^{+}+1\) := {\(k \in \mathbb{N} \| 3k + 1\)}&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If we expand it out, it becomes {1,4,7,10,13,16 …}&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In order to do induction on this set, we need change our base case and induction hypothesis a little bit. We need to have \(P(1)\) as base case and \(P(n) \implies P(n+3)\) as induction hypothesis instead. Can you see why? I think this is already a big hint for you homework problem so I’ll say no more. I’ll explain more on this in the modular arithmetic chapter!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/cs70/w3.gif&quot; alt=&quot;image info&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s a daily dose of kirara.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">The Truth Behind Induction Hypothesis:</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Note 002 Proofs (10 mins read)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/cs70/2020/06/13/note002.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Note 002 Proofs (10 mins read)" /><published>2020-06-13T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2020-06-13T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/cs70/2020/06/13/note002</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/cs70/2020/06/13/note002.html">&lt;h3 id=&quot;how-to-prove-an-implication-is-correct&quot;&gt;How to prove an implication is correct?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I got asked by this a lot: How do you prove “If P then Q”? You might encounter this question even bofore taking this class. And you probably know what to do, but don’t know why.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I can first assume P is true, and prove Q is true as well”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;YES! This is right procedure, your proof goes:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;”
Assume P is True,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some proofs…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conclude Q is true
“&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But do you know why I don’t you need to consider the case when P is False? After all, you just learnt “prove by cases”, there’s two cases for P, it can either be True or False. So why don’t we need to consider the case when P is False?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s two way to explain the answer:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, the intuitive way:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Consider this implication “If there’s a wild fire, the school will shut down.” When will this statement will false? It’s when in reality, there’s a wild fire, but school does not shut down. What if there’s no wild fire in the first place, then the school might not shut down due to other reason like the coronavirus. No matter what, it cannot prove the statement “If there’s a wild fire, the school will shut down.” is True or False. In other words, it’s irrelevant to the statment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next, the mathematical way, make sure, make sure you understand this, in fact, if you do, then your understanding is already above the curve:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Consider the Truth table for “If P then Q” aka, \(P \implies Q\)&lt;/p&gt;

\[\begin{array}{C|C|C|}
P &amp;amp; Q &amp;amp; P\implies Q \\
\hline
\color{red} T &amp;amp; \color{red}T &amp;amp; \color{red}T \\
T &amp;amp; F &amp;amp; F\\
\color{red}F &amp;amp; \color{red}T &amp;amp; \color{red}T\\
\color{red}F &amp;amp; \color{red}F &amp;amp; \color{red}T
\end{array}\]

&lt;p&gt;How do we prove \(p\implies q\) is true? We only need to consider the above three line that’s colored in red in the true table, which are all related to \(p \implies q\) being True. If we assume P is False, that goes to the the last two line, no matter what Q is, P will be True. If we assume P is True, we need to prove Q is true in order for \(P\implies Q\) to be True. That’s why we don’t bother to assume P is False. That’s why the general proving technique is:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;”
Assume P is True,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some proofs…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conclude Q is true
“&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/cs70/w2.gif&quot; alt=&quot;image info&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s a daily dose of kirara.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">How to prove an implication is correct?</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Note 001 Propositional Logic and Quantifiers (12 mins read)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/cs70/2020/06/13/note001.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Note 001 Propositional Logic and Quantifiers (12 mins read)" /><published>2020-06-13T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2020-06-13T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/cs70/2020/06/13/note001</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/cs70/2020/06/13/note001.html">&lt;h3 id=&quot;proposition-are-functions-that-takes-in-some-input-and-output-true-or-false&quot;&gt;Proposition are functions that takes in some input and output True or False:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example, we can define the proposition “x is greater than 5” as \(P(x)\). If we replace x with 4, it will make the statement becomes “4 is greater than 5”, a wrong statement. If we replace x with 6, it will make the statement becomes “6 is greater than 5”, a true statement. Wow, it’s just like a function in python :&lt;/p&gt;

\[P(x)= \left\{
\begin{array}{ll}
      True &amp;amp; x &amp;gt; 5\\
      False &amp;amp; x \leq 5\\
\end{array} 
\right.\]

&lt;p&gt;Similarly, “x is less than 6” can be written as \(Q(x)\) such that:&lt;/p&gt;

\[Q(x)= \left\{
\begin{array}{ll}
      True &amp;amp; x &amp;lt; 6\\
      False &amp;amp; x \geq 6\\
\end{array} 
\right.\]

&lt;p&gt;Further compounding proposition with logic will also give functions, for example:&lt;/p&gt;

\[Q(x) \wedge P(x) = \left\{
\begin{array}{ll}
      True &amp;amp; 5&amp;lt; x &amp;lt; 6\\
      False &amp;amp; Otherwise\\
\end{array} 
\right.\]

&lt;p&gt;Here’s today’s exercise: Prove the above expression is correct. Hint: use Truth Table (because this is the only way you learnt so far to prove things)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;what-exactly-is-universal-quantifier-forall-and-exists&quot;&gt;What exactly is Universal Quantifier \(\forall\) and \(\exists\):&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The \(\forall\) is a sequence of “and” and \(\exists\) is a sequence of “or”. Although this is in your note, I cannot stress it more. For example, we can denote the proposition “x is non-negative” as P(x). And what’s the statement “All natural number are non-negative” in propositional logic? It is&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;\((\forall n \in \mathbb{N}) P(n)\), which is equivalently as \(P(0) \wedge P(1) \wedge P(2) \wedge P(3) ...\)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Similarly, the statement “for any real number x, there is natural number greater than x” can be written as \((\forall x \in  \mathbb{R} ) (\exists n \in \mathbb{N}) x &amp;lt; n\), which can be expanded as \((\forall x \in \mathbb{R}) (x&amp;lt;1) \vee (x&amp;lt;2) \vee (x&amp;lt;3) \vee (x&amp;lt;4) ...\)
This is one of the most important theorem in anlysis, which is probably be the first thing you learn if you take Math 104. Notice I expaned \(\exists n \in \mathbb{N}\) using the “or” operator “\(\vee\)”, but I cannot expand \((\forall x \in  \mathbb{R} )\), this is simply because I cannot iterate through all the real number. Formally, real numbers are “uncountable” and we will learn about this later.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/cs70/w1.gif&quot; alt=&quot;image info&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s a daily dose of kirara.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Proposition are functions that takes in some input and output True or False:</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">General Tips</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/cs70/2020/06/13/note000.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="General Tips" /><published>2020-06-13T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2020-06-13T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/cs70/2020/06/13/note000</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/cs70/2020/06/13/note000.html">&lt;p&gt;For all the student who wants to get an A and A+ in this class, my advice is that simply watch lecture and doing practice exam is not enough. In order to get A and A+, you need to truly understand the material. You need to teach yourself and make a habit of reading notes. If you are interested in math/ML field, learn to read note/textbook will benefit you so much and even beyound the benefit of the material of this class. Another good way to study is to discuss among peers and explain the concept to your friend. Here’s some extra note I wrote for you to show that you truly understand the material. I love you all and wish you succeed!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/cs70/w0.gif&quot; alt=&quot;image info&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is Kirara(雲母) from an old school Anime called InuYasha. It isn’t my favorite anime but she is the cutest!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">For all the student who wants to get an A and A+ in this class, my advice is that simply watch lecture and doing practice exam is not enough. In order to get A and A+, you need to truly understand the material. You need to teach yourself and make a habit of reading notes. If you are interested in math/ML field, learn to read note/textbook will benefit you so much and even beyound the benefit of the material of this class. Another good way to study is to discuss among peers and explain the concept to your friend. Here’s some extra note I wrote for you to show that you truly understand the material. I love you all and wish you succeed!!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Note 005 Graph (5 mins read)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/cs70/2020/06/13/note004.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Note 005 Graph (5 mins read)" /><published>2020-06-13T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2020-06-13T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/cs70/2020/06/13/note004</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/cs70/2020/06/13/note004.html">&lt;h3 id=&quot;leap-of-the-faith&quot;&gt;Leap of the Faith:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For this chapter I think you really need to read the notes, not all the them, but if a theorem appears in the lecture. You should go back to find the proof for that theorem in the note and see if you understand it. A lot of you might ask if you need to remember the proofs. I will say, if you want an A, then the answer is Yes. However, remember the proofs does not mean reciting the proofs words for words, but remembering the most important line of the proof. I call this the “Leap of the Faith”. Here’s some example:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;theorem-51-eulers-theorem-1736-an-undirected-graph-g--ve-has-an-eulerian-tour-iff-g-is-even-degree-and-connected-except-possibly-for-isolated-vertices&quot;&gt;Theorem 5.1 (Euler’s Theorem (1736)): &lt;em&gt;An undirected graph G = (V,E) has an Eulerian tour iff G is even degree, and connected (except possibly for isolated vertices)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

\[\Rightarrow\]

&lt;p&gt;For a tour, we can imagine we removed an edge once we walked on it. For each vertex, the tour must go in and out. Since no edge is repeated, we remove two degree from the vertex each time. Eventually, we removed even number of degree for each vertex.&lt;/p&gt;

\[\Leftarrow\]

&lt;p&gt;Make a tour, still imagine we removed the edge that we walked on. Since every vertex has even degree, we must pass through every vertex and eventually comeback to the starting point. Repeat until we get an Eulerian tour.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/cs70/w4.gif&quot; alt=&quot;image info&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s a daily dose of kirara.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Leap of the Faith:</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">2020.05.23</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/birthday/2020/05/23/note009.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="2020.05.23" /><published>2020-05-23T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2020-05-23T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/birthday/2020/05/23/note009</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/birthday/2020/05/23/note009.html">&lt;p&gt;我的生日是昨天 现在美国的疫情很严重 因为疫情我从宿舍租的房子里搬到外面去住了 我合租的室友很希望我回去 但因为疫情我担心他们不够小心就以一直没回去 所以这天一整天我都在家里待着哪也没去 
因为是我的”生日“ 我不想工作 从早晨醒来 吃完饭再睡到中午 中午醒来一直没有字幕的看稲垣早希环游世界的那个日本电视节目 一直到半夜12点
但和去年完全相反 我不想联系任何人 如果这样 任何人都不知道我今天过生日 这是这么多年来我第一次有这个想法 
我想到这学期做Art期末Project里 引用之前trip review里的一句话 “我意识到我和自己是分开的 两码事 身体和我依赖的生存在这个世界上的一种形式 像是必要的 但也可能不是必须” 我想用这一天证明我能不依靠任何形式存在于这个世界上 这是这么多年来我第一次有这个想法 也可能是隔离到现在的成果吧 希望这个也能作为这个project的结语吧&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">我的生日是昨天 现在美国的疫情很严重 因为疫情我从宿舍租的房子里搬到外面去住了 我合租的室友很希望我回去 但因为疫情我担心他们不够小心就以一直没回去 所以这天一整天我都在家里待着哪也没去 因为是我的”生日“ 我不想工作 从早晨醒来 吃完饭再睡到中午 中午醒来一直没有字幕的看稲垣早希环游世界的那个日本电视节目 一直到半夜12点 但和去年完全相反 我不想联系任何人 如果这样 任何人都不知道我今天过生日 这是这么多年来我第一次有这个想法 我想到这学期做Art期末Project里 引用之前trip review里的一句话 “我意识到我和自己是分开的 两码事 身体和我依赖的生存在这个世界上的一种形式 像是必要的 但也可能不是必须” 我想用这一天证明我能不依靠任何形式存在于这个世界上 这是这么多年来我第一次有这个想法 也可能是隔离到现在的成果吧 希望这个也能作为这个project的结语吧</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">2020.04.18</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/dream_reality/2020/04/18/note001.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="2020.04.18" /><published>2020-04-18T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2020-04-18T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/dream_reality/2020/04/18/note001</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/dream_reality/2020/04/18/note001.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;color:red&quot;&gt; 
我梦见有一个住在一起的同学想杀我 他说他看不惯我做的事 说如果不住一起就罢了 但是住一起就要杀死我 梦无比清晰 知道最后醒来都是被吓醒的 而是接受了现实 他不知道为什么得到了从神那里拿到的贴纸 上面不同的颜色 有红色蓝色和绿色 红色是好运贴纸 蓝色是倒霉贴纸 他就是不断在我身上用蓝色贴纸 让我生活中的事一直变得对我不利
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;color:blue&quot;&gt; 
最后一次出门远足 发现一只鹿腿被卡到栅栏上死掉了 不叫也不挣扎 我们发现的时候皮肉干掉 没有腐败 头现一个自然的坑里 头周围居然一点草都没有长 青草充满敬意的张在坑外 让我想起Ana的Imagen de Yagul
&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;br /&gt; &amp;gt;
&lt;br /&gt; &amp;gt;
&lt;br /&gt; &amp;gt;
&lt;br /&gt; &amp;gt;
&lt;br /&gt; &amp;gt;
&lt;br /&gt; &amp;gt;
&lt;br /&gt; &amp;gt;
&lt;br /&gt; &amp;gt;
&lt;br /&gt; &amp;gt;
&lt;br /&gt; &amp;gt;
&lt;br /&gt; &amp;gt;
&lt;br /&gt; &amp;gt;
&lt;br /&gt; &amp;gt;
&lt;br /&gt; &amp;gt;
&lt;br /&gt; &amp;gt;
&lt;br /&gt; &amp;gt;
&lt;br /&gt; &amp;gt;
&lt;br /&gt; &amp;gt;
&lt;br /&gt; &amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/dream_reality/1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image info&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">我梦见有一个住在一起的同学想杀我 他说他看不惯我做的事 说如果不住一起就罢了 但是住一起就要杀死我 梦无比清晰 知道最后醒来都是被吓醒的 而是接受了现实 他不知道为什么得到了从神那里拿到的贴纸 上面不同的颜色 有红色蓝色和绿色 红色是好运贴纸 蓝色是倒霉贴纸 他就是不断在我身上用蓝色贴纸 让我生活中的事一直变得对我不利</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">2020.03.01</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/dream_reality/2020/03/01/note005.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="2020.03.01" /><published>2020-03-01T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2020-03-01T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/dream_reality/2020/03/01/note005</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/dream_reality/2020/03/01/note005.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;color:red&quot;&gt; 
Things start to melt beause they are
&lt;br /&gt;
The time is changing
&lt;br /&gt;
It will all be in a day
&lt;br /&gt;
You have focus on something
&lt;br /&gt;
Things will just fell apart
&lt;br /&gt;
The XXX effect is OK
&lt;br /&gt;
Trust him
&lt;br /&gt;
I felt the time is so long
&lt;br /&gt;
I’m protecting myself unconciously
&lt;br /&gt;
The time is not slow
&lt;br /&gt;
Go into another world is 
&lt;br /&gt;
You don’t wanna finish the sentence
&lt;br /&gt;
Everything start to fell apart
&lt;br /&gt;
But it’s good
&lt;br /&gt;
You can use an internel sense
&lt;br /&gt;
You have to find your own connection to get to another world
&lt;br /&gt;
Even written thing right now is a different world
&lt;br /&gt;
It felt good
&lt;br /&gt;
I understand a lot of things now
&lt;br /&gt;
Just trust written form
&lt;br /&gt;
Faulty loop
&lt;br /&gt;
But you can still get out of it
&lt;br /&gt;
You need some sensation to get you out of the world
&lt;br /&gt;
Music sense blend in with vision
&lt;br /&gt;
Do it
&lt;br /&gt;
Or not do it
&lt;br /&gt;
The react should not based on moving movement 
&lt;br /&gt;
Movement
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;color:blue&quot;&gt; 
我意识到我和自己是分开的 两码事 身体是我依赖的生存在这个世界上的一种形式 像是必须的 但也可能不是必须 我可以通过光 声音 空间 和时间等世界的本质去保证自己的存在
&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;br /&gt; &amp;gt;
&lt;br /&gt; &amp;gt;
&lt;br /&gt; &amp;gt;
&lt;br /&gt; &amp;gt;
&lt;br /&gt; &amp;gt;
&lt;br /&gt; &amp;gt;
&lt;br /&gt; &amp;gt;
&lt;br /&gt; &amp;gt;
&lt;br /&gt; &amp;gt;
&lt;br /&gt; &amp;gt;
&lt;br /&gt; &amp;gt;
&lt;br /&gt; &amp;gt;
&lt;br /&gt; &amp;gt;
&lt;br /&gt; &amp;gt;
&lt;br /&gt; &amp;gt;
&lt;br /&gt; &amp;gt;
&lt;br /&gt; &amp;gt;
&lt;br /&gt; &amp;gt;
&lt;br /&gt; &amp;gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/dream_reality/5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image info&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Things start to melt beause they are The time is changing It will all be in a day You have focus on something Things will just fell apart The XXX effect is OK Trust him I felt the time is so long I’m protecting myself unconciously The time is not slow Go into another world is You don’t wanna finish the sentence Everything start to fell apart But it’s good You can use an internel sense You have to find your own connection to get to another world Even written thing right now is a different world It felt good I understand a lot of things now Just trust written form Faulty loop But you can still get out of it You need some sensation to get you out of the world Music sense blend in with vision Do it Or not do it The react should not based on moving movement Movement</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">2019.05.23</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/birthday/2019/05/23/note008.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="2019.05.23" /><published>2019-05-23T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2019-05-23T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/birthday/2019/05/23/note008</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/birthday/2019/05/23/note008.html">&lt;p&gt;不知道为什么 这一天我特别希望和人在一起 我发了一条朋友圈要朋友来家里看真心为你 但电影开始之后又只想一个人待着 能真真切切的感受到AT field 整晚都觉得注意力集中不起来 除了绫波丽和碇的那句 梦是现实的延续 现实是梦的终结 其他什么都记不住了 以前没看懂的还是没看懂&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">不知道为什么 这一天我特别希望和人在一起 我发了一条朋友圈要朋友来家里看真心为你 但电影开始之后又只想一个人待着 能真真切切的感受到AT field 整晚都觉得注意力集中不起来 除了绫波丽和碇的那句 梦是现实的延续 现实是梦的终结 其他什么都记不住了 以前没看懂的还是没看懂</summary></entry></feed>